<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Eshotroid</string>
    
    <string name="weekDay">Week Days</string>
    <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
    <string name="sunday">Sunday</string>
    
    <string name="search_label">Bus Search</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Bus Number/Location</string>
    
    <string name="menu_more">More</string>
    <string name="menu_rate">Rate/Comment</string>
    <string name="menu_contact">Contact Developer</string>
    <string name="menu_website">Developer\'s Website</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About Application</string>
    
    <string name="pullToRefresh_pull">Pull to refresh.</string>
    <string name="pullToRefresh_release">Release to refresh.</string>
    <string name="pullToRefresh_refresh">Refreshing&#8230;</string>
    
    <string name="error_noConnection">No internet connection!</string>
    <string name="info_successful">Successful!</string>
    <string name="info_noTimes">No bus found for the specified day.</string>
    <string name="info_noClosestTime">No more bus to show. Showing all busses.</string>
    <string name="info_selectedTimePassed">The time has already passed for the bus you selected.</string>
    <string name="info_remainingTime">Remaining time for %1$s bus: %2$d hours %3$d minutes</string>
    
    <string name="title_favoritedBusses">Favorite Busses</string>
    <string name="title_allBusses">All Busses</string>
    
    <string name="contact_subject">About Eshotroid</string>
    
    <string name="help_title">Eshotroid Help</string>
    <string name="help_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="help_main_content">You can learn bus times easily with Eshotroid. Since every downloaded content is saved, the internet connection will only be needed while downloading bus list and checking times for a bus for the first time.\n\n* To easily find the bus you are looking for, you can use the search button on top right corner or you can add your favorite busses to the favorite busses list.\n\n* To add a bus to the favorite busses list, you can touch the star next to it.\n\n* To remove a bus from the favorite busses list, you can touch the star next to it again or you can touch and wait to its button in favorite busses list.\n\n* Times for the busses you add to favorite busses list get downloaded automatically (if there is internet connection) in the background.\n\n* If you want to download the bus list again, go to the top of bus list, pull the list down and release.</string>
    <string name="help_times_content">You can see the times for the bus you selected here.\n\n* To see the times for another day, simply change the selected day. Eshotroid, selects the appropriate day according to the current day by default.\n\n* You can see the remaining time for a bus by touching any time in the list.\n\n* To switch between showing all the times or just the ones from that time forward, you can use the time icon on top right corner. Eshotroid, shows the times from that time forward as default.\n\n* If you want to download the times for the selected day again, go to the top of times list, pull the list down and release.</string>
    
    <string name="about_title">About Eshotroid %1$s</string>
    <string name="about_content">&lt;p&gt;This application is developed by Mehmet Akif Tütüncü completely independent from &lt;b&gt;Eshot Genel Müdürlüğü&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All the bus information within the application is downloaded from &lt;b&gt;http://mobil.eshot.gov.tr&lt;/b&gt;. The developer does not guarantee that the information is correct and has no responsibility over the usage of the application.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This application is completely free. You can use it however you like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in the source codes of the application, you can send an e-mail about this to the developer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please let the developer know about your opinions, suggestions and errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hope you never miss your bus&#8230; :)&lt;/p&gt;</string>
    <string name="about_ok">OK</string>

</resources>